Krace

Profile

Chinese Name:

吳逸凡 (Yi-Fan, Wu)

English Name:

Krace

Contact

Email:

krace710267@gmail.com

Github:

https://github.com/DemonicKrace

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/krac e-demonic-039021133/

Language:

Chinese – Native English – TOEIC 620

Hobbies

- Financial investment research
- Crypto market and blockchain following
- Part time programming tutor
- World & social news tracking
- Movie, Animation, TV series, Novel, Music, Song

Summary

System engineer with 5 years of experience in software development for platforms. Versed in system infrastructure to alleviate pitfalls inherent to on-site computing. Provider of smooth, well-planned transition architecture. Familiar with web API development and database maintenance. Practiced at building appropriate SOP of routine work to Start-up team.

Skill Highlights

- Web-based backend
- High problem fix
- Architecture Design
- InfoSec awareness
- Database maintenances
- Team communication

Experience

Sr. System Engineer | inFluxFin Technology Inc. Taipei, 2020/03 - 2021/05

- Manage servers on AWS, emergency event hotfix
- Design and refactor old systems to microservice, enhance system security
- Fix existing problem, develop P2P-ERP accounting system
- API develop (OCR, Scraper, p2p-loan product, encrypt model)
- Project Cooperation, integrate third-party service (Bank, Government)
- Optimize core system of trade platform
- instruct newbies and interns

Web & System Developer | Synology Inc. New Taipei, 2018/10 - 2019/12

- Internal system development and security problem fix
- System update (Language, Framework, Plugins, third-party packages)
- Deployment environment and database migrate
- Tech document writing

Software Engineer | Institute for Information Industry. Taipei, 2017/07 – 2018/08

- Startup project develop and design (IoT service, Node.js)
- Unity App integrate (third-plugins, tensorflow & keras model to Xcode)

Software Engineer | **PICK International Asset Management Co., Ltd,** New Taipei, 2016/07 - 2016/12

• Internal system development and maintenance

University-Industry cooperation | Taiwan Network Information Center, 2014 - 2017

• IPv6 software & hardware supported system develop, GOV. tech support

Education

MS: Computer and Communication Engineer - $2016/09 \sim 2018/08$, Ming Chuan University, A Research of Indoor Positioning Systems Using Terrestrial Magnetism

Achievement

2013/07/03: ACM ICPC at CGU University.

2013/10/01: CPE online competition, Rank: class A & 98th/819.

2013/12/24: Microsoft MTA certificate.

2015/03/19: Maker x iBeacon.

2015/03/21: ideaXD X Hackathon at FJCU University, Best Creative Award by team.

2015/03/29: Hackathon at TKU University.

2015/04/12: Hackathon at NCTU University, Best Creative Award by team.

2015/08/11: OpenStack Day Taiwan 2015.

2015/10/15: TWNIC School APP Show Competition 2015, Rank 5th.

2016/04/01: SUSE Expert Day 2016.

2017/05/03: Taiwan University Software Application Competition 2017, Honorable Mention Award.

2017/10/03: Seminar of Taiwan Academic Network(TANet), number: 6905.

2019/10-11: AWS Workshop Hack 'n' Roll: CDK & CouldFormation, Domain Driven

Design. Kubernetes. AWS & Twitch Hackathon.